{
    "subject": "Zofia_Czartoryska",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Stanis\u0142aw_Kostka_Zamoyski",
    "human_readable": "Zofia Czartoryska is married to Stanis\u0142aw Kostka Zamoyski.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9885410666465759,
            "question": "Is there a known marriage between Zofia Czartoryska and Stanis\u0142aw Kostka Zamoyski?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.972908079624176,
            "question": "Name the spouse of Zofia Czartoryska."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9609270691871643,
            "question": "Who is married to Stanis\u0142aw Kostka Zamoyski?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9603657126426697,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the relationship between Zofia Czartoryska and Stanis\u0142aw Kostka Zamoyski?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9500675201416016,
            "question": "Who is Stanis\u0142aw Kostka Zamoyski married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9141144752502441,
            "question": "What is the nature of the relationship between Zofia Czartoryska and Stanis\u0142aw Kostka Zamoyski?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9042404890060425,
            "question": "What is the name of Zofia Czartoryska's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8808987140655518,
            "question": "Is Zofia Czartoryska in a marital relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8364539742469788,
            "question": "To whom is Zofia Czartoryska connected?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23587113618850708,
            "question": "Who are the individuals involved in this marriage?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Zofia Czartoryska is married to Stanis\u0142aw Kostka Zamoyski.",
            "html": "yago_7341_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To whom is Zofia Czartoryska connected?",
            "html": "yago_7341_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Zofia Czartoryska in a marital relationship?",
            "html": "yago_7341_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Zofia Czartoryska's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_7341_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7341_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7341_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7341_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7341_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7341_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7341_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7341_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7341_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7341_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7341_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the documents, I can confirm that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that confirms Princess Zofia Czartoryska was married to Stanis\u0142aw Kostka Zamoyski, as indicated in the text from \"38.txt\": \"He married Princess Zofia Czartoryska on May 20, 1798 in Pu\u0142awy.\" and \"70.txt\": \"She married Stanis\u0142aw Kostka Zamoyski on 20 May 1798, at Pu\u0142awy.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}